This series is crafted for the purpose of entertainment.
All characters, behaviors, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
[7HD Channel]
[iQIYI]
[Present]
♫Where’s that love people are saying?♫
♫To always be by each other’s sides♫
♫The love that’s willing to sacrifice everything♫
♫Everything even my own life♫
♫Do they really exist? I’d rather not believe it♫
♫I don’t think I’ll ever fall for anyone♫
♫Love? I don’t find it interesting♫
♫Sorry about that♫
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
[Flaming Chains of Love]
[Previously]
I heard you went to the mine yesterday.
You told your sister to count rocks, and even let her work under the sun.
It was just to practise her patience.
By throwing away her bike and letting her walk to work?
You also made her go through all the accounting papers until late at night.
Are you sure you didn’t try to pick on her?
Boo!
Shit!
There’s no hole? Did I punch her too hard she’s gone bonkers?
I want you to take Kaphrao with you to the opening of Nam’s new resort.
Why would you want me to take this Gremlin with me?
I don’t want to go!
If you don’t want to go, then that’s all right.
While Fai is away, I’ll be your coach at work instead, okay?
I’ve changed my mind. I’ll take Guinea Pig to Hua Hin too.
Here, freshen up a bit.
Can you stop making a grumpy face?
I’m taking you to congratulate my sister, not to a slaughterhouse.
Try to act more human.
But I don’t want to go.
Why did you change your mind and tell Uncle like that?
It’s fun to see someone being grumpy.
Maniac!
I have three older sisters.
Who asked you?
I’m just saying it–so that you won’t do something stupid and embarrass me in front of my sisters.
No need.
Uncle already told me everything.
You probably acted all innocent and sucked up to my dad to pry it out of him.
It’s lucky I decided to drag you out with me.
Otherwise, you’d have had chances to seduce him more.
Seriously, is your brain only full of crap?
I’m telling you for the umpteenth time–I love and respect Uncle like a father!
He’s my dad not yours. Stop stealing someone else’s dad.
You’re jealous? Are you eight years old or what?
Hey, watch it! I’m older than you.
Why?
It’s true though–can’t you accept it? So childish.
Go back to your seat, chauffeur.
Should I just let her walk there?
[Door knocking]
Akanee, why did you allow that girl to go to Hua Hin with Fai?
It's training for work, and also to get to know Fai’s cousins.
That girl is an outsider. Why would you want to introduce her to them?
Kaphrao is Fai’s assistant. She’s supposed to know everything so that it’d be easier when they work together.
Really? I think you actually want to introduce her to everyone in your family.
What are you trying to say, Panee?
You’ve always treated Kaphrao as if she were your own child.
You’re being nonsense.
I’m just fond of her. I feel pity for her because she’s an orphan.
Don’t be so biased and narrow-minded.
Fine then. You’d better make sure she wouldn’t do anything to hurt my niece.
Or else she’ll pay for it!
[LADARA Resort&Spa]
Please tell the reservation team to recheck all the bookings carefully, especially for those during the high season.
Yes, Boss.
[Fai]: Nam! Lada!
Oh, you’re here?
Congratulations, Sis.
I bought this super-size banquet especially for you.
Thanks a lot.
May your new business grow and make you a thousand times richer.
But maybe not as rich as Young Master Fai.
Uncle Ak owns a lot more businesses than I do.
Well, he might have plenty but many of his side pieces are also trying to get their hands on his money.
Let me help you with that, Nam.
[Nam]: Careful, it’s heavy.
Excuse me, can you put this in her office?
[Staff]: Yes, Boss.
[Lada]: Thank you.
This is the Guinea Pig–I mean, Athittaya. You can call her Kaphrao.
She’s one of Dad’s kept women.
She just graduated so he wants her to help with work.
This is my sister, Nam–and my sister-in-law, Lada.
Hello, Miss Nam and Miss Lada.
You’ve come all the way here, why don’t you stay a bit longer?
I have to leave the day after tomorrow. I’m worried about work.
What? Since when have you started to worry about work?
So, where are Din, Lom, and the others?
Din and Rose already arrived.
But Lom and Miss Blew are still in Madelin–they couldn’t make it in time.
Geez, I thought the Watinwanich sisters would be all present this time.
Well…
You must be tired from a long drive.
Let me show you to your room.
[Fai]: Give me your biggest room.
- [Nam]: I know.
Let’s go. Do you like it here?
It’s wonderful.
Guinea Pig!
Hurry up and get changed. My sisters and I will go out for dinner.
I’m not going.
You can go and spend time with your Watinwanich family all you like.
My sisters told me to invite you. Or else, I wouldn’t have asked.
But I don’t know any of them.
You already met Nam and Lada.
If you don’t go, I’ll tell Dad that you don’t show my sisters respect.
No manners.
Fine! I’ll go–so that you’ll shut up.
Why are you following me?
I’m afraid you’ll ditch.
You, freak!
Wear something pretty. Don’t dress up like a servant!
Annoying!
[Lada]: Do you like it?
[Din]: It’s splendid.
[Lada]: Wait until you try the food, it’s amazing.
[Rose]: I can’t wait.
- [Fai]: Wow!
The view here is fantastic!
Finally, what took you so long?
Someone’s been dawdling.
Please have a seat.
Thank you.
Is this the girl you told me she came with Fai?
Yes.
I didn’t want her to come with me though.
Dad made me do it.
I’m Rose. And that’s Din.
Hello.
I’m Kaphrao, or you can just call me Phrao.
Okay.
You have quite a unique name.
And also a very sweet-looking face. Don’t you think so, Din?
I think she looks really cute.
Thank you.
Let’s order something then, shall we?
Can we have the menu?
Thank you.
You must be very close to Fai, Miss Phrao.
I don’t usually see her go somewhere with anyone.
It’s not like that. Uncle told her to bring me here too.
She didn’t have a choice but to comply.
Weird, isn’t it?
Usually, Fai is so stubborn to Uncle Ak.
She never listens to him.
That’s right. Nam told me Fai and her father always fight.
Isn’t that right?
So, are you and Fai dating, Miss Phrao?
No!
No, Boss Rose!
There’s no way I’d be interested in her. She’s ugly and not even a bit cute.
She also loves to fix things with her fists. Who the hell in their right mind would like her?
Besides, I don’t want anything to do with Dad’s side chick.
I’d rather stay single forever than have this Gremlin as a girlfriend!
Please excuse me, I need to go to the loo.
Too ashamed to listen to it?
What should I order?
Hmm, they have quite a lot on the menu.
Oh, this one looks good, right?
Does she think she’s so good-looking herself? Buffalo Fai!!!
I’m sorry! Please don’t mind me.
Aren’t you guys going to eat? They’re all delicious.
Why are you all looking at me like that?
Seriously, you still have no idea?
About what? I don’t like her. Why would I say otherwise?
Then, just keep it to yourself.
You don’t have to be so harsh to her.
What if someone says those things to you, how would you feel?
And don’t you dare argue you were just being blunt.
What you did was nothing but rude.
Did all those words even pass through your brain before they came out of your mouth?
You need to stop doing that, Fai.
Please be more careful with your words.
Once spoken, they cannot be changed or taken back.
Just like the feelings of the receiving end–already hurt and broken.
Boss Rose, you’re my only hope now.
You understand me, don’t you?
No, I don’t.
I wasn't Miss Phrao but even I felt so hurt and taken aback.
No one on earth would like it.
No wonder why you’re still single.
And if you like her but don’t know how to say it so you just keep picking on her–that’s so outdated.
If she says she hates you, then she means it.
Lada, maybe–
Don’t try to stop me.
It’s because you never give her a serious reprimand,
that’s why she never grows up.
If you ever say something like that to me, I’d definitely break up with you.
You guys are ganging up on me.
I’m out of here.
My ears have gone numb.
Good job, Lada.
Silly Gremlin.
[Door knocking]
Go away! I’m not your bloody Gremlin!
S…Sorry.
Where are you going, lady?
Are you in a hurry?
What’s your name?
Hey, what the hell!
Get off me!
You like it tough, huh?
Quite stubborn, aren’t you?
Let me go!
Hey! Can’t you see she doesn’t want to talk to you?
Fai!
Wanna have fun too, huh?
Have fun, my foot!
Smart mouth, aren’t you? What’s your name, girl?
Go ask your mother then!
Hey! I asked you nicely!
I’ll count ‘one, two…’
[Younger Fai]: I’ll count ‘one, two…’ After three, just run.
[Kaphrao’s crying]
[Fai]: Get off me!
[Kaphrao]: Fai, I’m scared!
Don’t you want a doll?
I’m taking you to get it.
I don’t want it anymore. I’m scared!
If you don’t stop crying, I’ll leave you here alone.
Fai, don’t leave me!
[Screaming]
Fai! Please don’t leave me, Fai!
Fai!
[Crying]
Fai..
Let's go.
I’ll count ‘One, two…’ After three, just run, okay?
I can’t run.
One.
Two.
Three!
[Screaming]
Go after them!
Hurry up! Faster!
Out of the way! Damn it!
- Boo!
- [Screaming]
[Panting]
We’ve probably lost them.
They’re that drunk.
I didn’t expect you’d help.
I didn’t mean to.
I only did what any good person would do in that situation.
And I thought you would start throwing punches at them.
Are you nuts? I’m not that stupid. It’s 3:1, I would’ve got myself buried under their feet.
No wonder you were running for life back there.
What? I just needed some time to muster up.
I see. You sure took a long time, huh?
But thank you anyway.
Just leave it there. I don’t want it.
Just stop getting into trouble.
Let’s go back.
Hey, isn’t that Kaphrao?
Come on, let’s get her!
Ugly Kaphrao! A stray kid with no parents!
I have Uncle Ak.
Abandoned kid, no one wants you!
- Abandoned kid, no one–
- [Fai]: Stop it!
Stop bullying her!
Fai…
You fool! Haven’t I told you not to be weak?
You, second grade, stay out of this!
No! Are you going to stop?
No!
Kaphroa has no father! Kaphrao has no mother!
[Fai]: I said stop it!
[Bullies]: Kaphrao has no mother!
Ouch!
Ouch! Stop it! Get off me!
Come on, get up.
Are you going to stop?
I’ll go tell the teacher!
Get lost, losers! You, rotten jerks!
That’s all right. I can get up on my own.
Why are you following me?
Just go to your room.
I want to make sure you won’t go out to cause any trouble again.
Annoying.
Why? Don’t you want to hear my pretty voice?
I’m telling you, I used to be a singer when I was still in college.
Ew!
Hang on.
What now?
I’m sorry I said bad things to you.
Mhm, I’m used to it.
She can talk nicely too, huh?
I’m really sorry.
Miss Phrao.
Miss Rose, good morning.
Please don’t do that.
You went for a jog since early morning?
A woman should never stop glowing.
Right.
What will you wear to the party tonight?
Well, I’m afraid I won’t attend it.
Why not?
I didn’t bring any party dress with me.
That’s all right. You can wear mine–I’ve brought lots of them.
Oh, I’d rather not. I…I…
Don’t worry. Just come to my room, okay?
I’ll make you the most beautiful woman tonight.
You can’t be serious.
I am!
[Fai]: She’s so ugly–not even a bit cute.
[Fai]: She loves to fix things with her fists. Who, in their right mind, would like her?
I’m not that pretty.
Are you still thinking about last night?
Please ignore what Fai said.
I’ll make her take back every single word.
Please trust me. It’ll be great.
♫But then who are you?♫
♫To make my heart keep fluttering♫
♫Please tell me♫
♫What’s happening with my heart?♫
♫It can’t be, why am I feeling this?♫
♫Oh, my heart is pounding so fast♫
♫Time freezes whenever I see you♫
♫I wonder why every time you smile♫
♫Something in your eyes make me go weak♫
♫Oh no, this is real–it’s not a dream♫
♫Or is the love that people are saying...♫
♫Is it you?♫
It’s done.
Wow! You look completely different.
Isn’t it too heavy?
It’s beautiful.
I usually work in the mine or plantation.
I don’t know who I should look pretty for.
It’s for yourself. No need to do it for anyone.
So that when we look at ourselves in the mirror, we could be proud of our own beauty from inside out.
Do you like it?
Yes.
So pretty.
[LADARA Resort & Spa]
Listen, Rose gave Phrao her best dress and it looks so pretty on her!
But maybe she’s never curled her hair before. She looks quite stiff and nervous.
But, overall, she looks really pretty.
Ha! I guess Boss Rose must be having a headache by now.
Why in the world would she try to give that monkey a makeover?
Hey, what’s so bad about Phrao?
I think she’s cute for her age.
That’s it, Din. I’m going to tell Boss Rose you compliment other girls.
What? Why can’t I compliment her? She’s really cute.
I sent Lom a picture of her and she also said Phrao is cute.
That’s because you guys are getting old and have bad eyesights.
How the heck can you find her cute?
I’m going nuts!
Yeah, she’s not cute.
There! You see?
Even Nam agrees with me this time.
But she’s beautiful.
Your mouth is so wide open a bunch of flies can get in.
Close it.
Isn’t she pretty, Fai?
Ye–
She’s just okay.
Not that pretty.
I’ll go find something to eat first.
If you call a girl that pretty ‘just okay’,
I guess your type is probably as high as the moon.
But I think she looks so beautiful tonight. Look at her.
Trust me, some guys will be lining up to talk to her soon.
Good evening.
Sorry for intruding, but are you here alone?
Look what I just said.
I’ll just…excuse myself then.
Would you like to join me at the table?
Maybe not.
Why are you following me?
What? Who’s following you? I’m here to get something to eat too.
Don’t be so full of yourself.
I’ll go get some air outside. Don’t follow me.
Look at her. She said she doesn’t care but she keeps following her like a puppy.
Should’ve given her head a shake, so she’d finally come to her senses.
She definitely needs it.
But maybe, having Miss Phrao by her side might help make her life better.
Coming out for air, huh? Why walking barefoot like you’re filming for an MV?
Why the hell would you follow me? Just go talk to your sisters.
No, it’s too crowded there.
Look, if you’re going to pick a fight with me again–just go back inside.
Why are you staring at me?
Do you have eyes on your head?
No.
See? Definitely a death stare.
You’re a nuisance–always causing trouble.
That’s why you hate me, isn’t it?
If you hate me, why don’t we just mind our own business? Why keep following me around just to pick a fight?
Who said I hate you?
You did, both through your words and actions.
Even now when we’re talking, you can’t stand looking at me.
When did I tell you that I hate you?
When we were young, you always said it.
And when was the last time I said it?
ut you can believe it all you like since you hate me too. We’re even then.
I actually don’t hate you–I just don’t like you.
How’s that different?
There! That’s what I don’t like–always ready to explode like a walking fireball.
Then, do you expect me to sit back and laugh at it when someone says they don’t like me?
If you want them to like you, then try to be nice.
If you can quit being so hot-tempered and headstrong, and try to be more mature;
I’m sure someone will definitely be interested in you.
It’s not like I want anyone to be interested in me.
Phrao!
Are you Kaphrao?
Nod!
[Squealing with joy]
[Kaphrao]: I miss you!
[Nod]: Phrao! Never thought I’d see you here!
[Kaphrao]: Yeah! I’m so happy!
This is Fai, my boss.
This is Nod, my close friend.
Hello.
[Kaphrao]: Aww, miss you so much!
[Nod]: You look so skinny.
[Kaphrao]: Really?
- [Nod]: Have you lost weight?
[Nod]: Aww, why? Are you on a diet?
You have to treat me to a meal then.
Sure, what do you want to eat?
Pork leg!
Whatever you say!
So, we haven’t met since we graduated, right?
That’s because you went to study abroad.
So, how come you’re invited to the party too?
My uncle also owns a hotel, so he and Miss Nam know each other.
That’s why she invited us.
What about you?
Fai is Miss Nam’s cousin.
I’m working with her in Surat Thani, so I just tag along here.
I see. So, you’ve moved to Surat.
That’s why none of our friends have heard from you.
That’s because I don’t do social media.
I also got a new number so I’ve lost all the contacts and didn’t call anyone.
I thought so. It was just the two of us back then, remember?
Yeah.
Looks like you two are really close, huh?
Absolutely!
We were inseparable back then, right?
Yes.
We played together, studied together, ate together, and even shared the same bed.
Our teachers often called us the twins of Siam.
We even went to the toilet together.
Oh, and we used to sneak out at night and fall off the dorm too.
[Kaphrao]: Nod, don’t! That’s TMI.
- [Nod]: Back then, you were–
[Kaphrao]: Stop it, Nod.
[Nod]: Why? It’s so funny.
I’m tired. I’m going back to my room.
Go then. Why are you telling me?
Dad told me to look after you. How could I leave you here alone?
What if anything happens like last night?
If I’m leaving, you have to come with me.
But I still want to catch up with my friend here.
But I need to sleep!
Then, leave!
It’s all right, Phrao.
If she wants you to go back with her,
why don’t we go talk in your room after this?
Sure, that’s great!
You can just come with me then.
Deal! We’ll spend all night catching up and reminiscing on our good old days.
Let’s go then, so we’ll have more time.
Okay.
I have so many things to tell you.
They’re sharing a bed?
[I’m so happy to see you, Phrao.]
[I need to tell you something.]
[What is it?]
[I really miss you.]
[Nod…]
Shit!
[Giggling]
Why are you nodding off here?
Waiting for you, of course.
Why?
So…we can walk to the car together.
Hold on. Where’s your friend?
Already left since last night.
Better be gone for good.
What was that?
Nothing. Let’s go.
Nod!
Are you leaving? I’m here to see you off.
Come, let me help.
Oh, it’s all right.
That’s fine. It’s nothing.
Thank you.
You’re the sweetest!
What do you want to eat?
[Mocking] You’re the sweetest!
Young Master, the Big Boss wants you both to go see him. He needs to talk to you about something.
Can you tell Dad we’ll go talk to him tomorrow?
I’m so exhausted from the trip.
This Gremlin’s driving skill completely sucks–I could barely sleep.
Why didn’t you drive it yourself?
It’s all right.
I’m not tired.
I can go see him now.
Hold it right there!
Suddenly wagging your tail to suck up to him, huh?
If you don’t want to go, then stay here. I’ll go.
Are you finding an excuse to be alone with my dad?
B.N.R!
What?
Bloody Nerve-Racking!
Then stop flirting around.
Save your stinking breath!
Just go to bed if you’re sleepy, so that you won’t lash out on me.
I’ll only leave if you do.
You!
All right then, why don’t you go talk to him tomorrow? I’ll let the Master know.
Okay. Please walk her home and make sure she gets in the house.
Don’t let her sneak out to seduce my dad.
Go then. I’ll wait until you’re out of my sight.
Ouch! That was harsh.
Let me help you, Miss.
Please excuse me.
Whose bag is this?
Mine.
Here you go, Young Master.
Let’s go.
What’s wrong?
I’m home n–
Aww, Auntie, Auntie, Auntie, Auntie!
My lovely Auntie.
Talk to me first, Pretty Lady.
Hmm, are you still mad at me?
Do you still care? You hardly listen to me these days.
Who told you that? I’ll always be your good girl, Auntie.
Then, why didn’t you listen to me this time?
Why did you take that girl with you?
Because Dad made me do it.
You usually never listen to whatever he says.
I’m following your advice.
You told me to keep an eye on her, and never leave her alone with Dad.
Remember?
But, right now, it’s different.
What if that girl changes her mind and tries to get her hands on you instead? What would you do?
Come on, Auntie. Where did you get that idea from?
That’s impossible. She hates me to her guts.
So funny.
Then, promise me you’ll never fall for her.
Yes, I’ll never fall for anyone. I’ll stay with you forever.
I’ll let you take care of me until I’m old, okay?
Can you live until then?
Come, let’s go to sleep. It’s late.
I was so exhausted earlier but seeing you just freshen me up.
Give me a peck. Come on, let’s go.
Can I sleep in your room tonight?
Mhm.
Please come in.
By the way, I forgot to ask.
How was the trip with Young Master? Did you enjoy it?
You two didn’t fight all the way home, did you?
You wish. It’s lucky we got back safely.
Oh, was it that bad? Quite disappointing though.
I thought you and Young Master would finally become close again, just like the old days.
That will never happen, Uncle Yod.
Well, who knows?
Young Master usually doesn’t like to be with anyone except Miss Panee.
But after you came here, she’s been hanging out with you quite often lately.
The only reason she agrees to hang out with me is because she wants to keep an eye on me and nitpick me on everything I do!
So…
Why would Uncle want me to go see him tomorrow?
I also don’t have the faintest idea.
I hope he won’t assign me to a job that would put me through another hell with that Buff–Fai again.
I also hope it won’t be like that.
I’m leaving then.
Thank you so much, Uncle Yod.
- Have a nice evening.
- Yes.
Do you remember that show where they interviewed Miss Blew about her life while she was staying on our island?
After it aired, many people have expressed interest in visiting there.
Yeah, Nam also mentioned it to me when I met her in Hua Hin.
That’s why I plan to build some accommodations there,
and turn our island into an ecotourism attraction.
This is the plan I’ve written in detail.
I want you and Kaphrao to go there to see if there’s anything else we could improve.
Me and Kaphrao?
Yes.
What does that have to do with her?
Well,
I want you and Kaphrao to look after this project together.
I already told Boonsong. You can go talk to him tomorrow, okay?
Can’t you tell the time? I said let’s meet at 7.
It’s now 6.55–that’s not 7 yet.
You’re here early. Can’t blame me.
Save your excuses. My legs are growing roots here.
Really? Where?
I don’t see a single root here.
It can almost strangle your neck.
Aww, where is it? So scary!
Guinea Pig!
What? You started it first.
Get in the car.
What? Have a problem?
[Fai]: Hey, I’m not driving. We’re not driving there.
[Kaphrao]: Fine, then don’t. It’s not like I want you to go.
[Fai]: Good, close the door then.
- [Kaphrao]: Okay!
Bye!
Don’t come out then.
Oh, why are you sweating?
Are you sweating?
I’ll go to the loo then.
[Staff]: Hello, what petrol would you like?
Diesel, fill up the tank please.
What is it?
Shit!
I’m so sorry.
Young Master, I really miss my parents so I decided to sneak into your car.
It’s not a big deal at all, you could’ve just asked her nicely, Bua.
Well, I…I was afraid you mightn’t let me come with you.
Your Young Master is probably not that heartless.
Right?
Young Master, please let me go with you too.
I promise I’ll behave. Please!
Please, Young Master! Please…let me go with you too.
Please, please, please! Let me go with you.
[Bua]: Please, please, please!
[Fai]: Okay, fine!
We’ve already come this far, I guess I don’t have a choice.
I wouldn’t go all the way back just to drop you off.
Aww, Young Master, you’re the best indeed!
Can I go sit in the car then?
It’s bloody hot up here. You hardly stop by anywhere.
Huh, my fault then?
Wait for me too.
I’m coming.
How could you stand the heat?
Right?
I don’t get it either.
Hi, everyone! Hello, there!
Thank you so much for watching me LIVE today.
Wow, you guys just keep flooding in the minute I come online–as if you’ve been waiting for this moment.
Please don’t forget to click LIKE and SHARE for me, and SUBSCRIBE too.
Thanks for watching me LIVE today. I’ve come on land to try the coffee at a new coffee shop.
Wow! It’s really good. Maybe I should open a branch on the island.
Just comment if you have any idea about it.
- Yeah, okay?
- [Bua]: Dad!
Dad!
- Bua?
- Daddy! I miss you so much!
All right, all right. I know it. So…
Don’t you have to work today? Why are you here?
Are you skipping work?
Geez, Dad. I’ve already asked Young Master and she agreed.
[Bua]: Aww, Dad. Miss you!
[Boonsong]: Young Master is generous.
Are you sure you’ve asked?
Hello, Young Master.
Hello.
This is Kaphrao, an assistant Dad has sent to help me.
Kaphrao, this is Uncle Boonsong–the head of Fisherman’s Village on my dad’s island.
And he’s also my father.
Hello, Uncle Boonsong.
Hello, Miss Kaphrao.
Dad, why don’t we go talk over there instead? It’s hot here.
Yeah, it’s quite hot here.
Right? Come on then. Let’s go over there.
Let’s go. Oh, I’m still on LIVE!
[Bua]: Oh, okay.
[Boonsong]: That’s it for today then.
Say bye, everyone! Bye!
I’ll see you later.
You’re addicted to it now.
Let’s go.
I have nothing to do.
Aww, miss you so much!
[Boonsong]: If it’s still hot there, should we go talk in the water then?
[Bua]: No! Let’s not do that.
Here, please have a look at it first.
Thank you.
Dad wants to know if you think it’s possible to open a small homestay on the island,
promote ecotourism there, and have the villagers run everything by themselves.
I think if the number of tourists is quite small, the villagers can definitely manage.
Just like when Miss Lom and Miss Blew stayed there.
We can start off with just a few cottages first.
Maybe, we shouldn’t focus on making profits, but rather creating income for the villagers.
What do you think?
That’s wonderful then.
I’ll go talk to the villagers and explain the idea to them.
By the way, do you need to go to the island? If so, I’ll go get the boat ready.
That’s all right.
I go there quite often. I already have an idea what needs to be done here.
Yes.
Too bad then. I thought you’d take Miss Phrao to see the island.
So that she’d know what it’s like there.
You’ve never been there, Miss Phrao?
No. I really want to go there.
Why would you want to go there?
There’s no facilities on the island and it’s not as convenient as you think.
I guarantee if you go there, you’ll get bored the moment your feet touch the sand.
But Uncle has assigned me to this project, so I’m supposed to go inspect the area.
Otherwise, how would you expect me to work?
I want to go there!
But Young Master won’t be coming with us today.
That’s fine. I can go with Bua.
Well, then…
You’re welcome.
[Bua]: How is it, Dad? Sweet?
[Boonsong]: Yeah, bittersweet.
- [Bua]: I see.
[Next Episode]
Wow!
[Fai]: This place holds a lot of memories between Lom and Miss Blew.
Is there anything else that we can use as a selling point?
We have pink shells here.
If you find it, you’ll get to make a wish.
What the hell?
There’s a cave over there. Let’s go!
What? Suddenly pouring down like this?
When I want to be secluded, I’d either set up a tent somewhere on the island or sleep in this cave.
You think you’re a hermit or what?
It’s called being Indie*. (*Independent)
What? Does that mean we won’t be able to leave until tomorrow?
If you’re not going to sleep, stay up and keep watch until morning then.
[Miming] Go downstairs.
♫I still remember vividly that day when we first met♫
♫Those memories we had together never fade away from my heart♫
♫We might never say it out loud how we feel for each other♫
♫But deep down we both know how we feel♫
♫Those things in the past, I still can’t forget them♫
♫I want to know if you’re like that too–do you also feel the same?♫
♫I could never forget those eyes of yours♫
♫The warmth you used to give me, I still remember it vividly♫
♫No matter for how long, you’ll always remain in my heart♫
♫All those years I’ve been waiting, for us to finally be together again♫
[North Star Entertainment]
[Flaming Chains of Love]